debtconsolidationcare.com 2016-06-20

# Privacy Policy | www.debtconsolidationcare.com

Effective from 9th April, 2010

## Our commitment to protect your privacy

At Debt Consolidation Care, we understand that your privacy is important and we make sure it is protected. In our privacy policy, we try and explain our online information practices - what information we collect from you and how we use and protect your information on our website.

## The information we collect from you

This applies to personal information collected or submitted on our website with your knowledge. The information collected includes:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Best time to call (etc.)

## The way we use your information

At Debt Consolidation Care, we do not share your information with outside parties except when it is required for your help. We use return email addresses to answer emails we receive from you. However, such email addresses are not shared with outside parties and are not used for any other purpose.

You can register with our website if you need free counseling or you wish to participate in our community. But the information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

## Our commitment to maintain data security 

To ensure the correct use of your information, maintain data accuracy and prevent unauthorized access to your information, we have implemented physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect and secure the information collected online from you.

## Our commitment to protect the privacy of children

We believe that protecting the privacy of children is important. Hence we do not collect or maintain information from those who're under 13. We also make sure that no section of our website is developed to attract those under 13.

## You can access or correct your information

You can access all your personal information that we collect online and maintain on our website. This is to make sure that you can correct any factual errors and protect your information better.

To protect your privacy and security, we take steps to verify your identity before giving access or allowing you to correct any error in your information.

## How you can contact us

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please call **800-debt-913** or send us an email at **vikas(at)debtconsolidationcare.com**.
